earticleblog.com 2018-09-06

# Privacy Policy - Earticleblog

Privacy Policy -EarticleBlog

## **Privacy Policy for www.earticleblog.com**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at newtweeks@gmail.com.

At www.earticleblog.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.earticleblog.com and how it is used. ** **

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, www.earticleblog.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

### Use of Cookies

This website uses cookies to better the users experience while visiting the website. Where applicable this website uses a cookie control system allowing the user on their first visit to the website to allow or disallow the use of cookies on their computer/device. This complies with recent legislation requirements for websites to obtain explicit consent from users before leaving behind or reading files such as cookies on a user’s computer/device.

This website uses tracking software to monitor its visitors to better understand how they use it. This software is provided by Google Analytics which uses cookies to track visitor usage. The software will save a cookie to your computers hard drive in order to track and monitor your engagement and usage of the website, but will not store, save or collect personal information. You can read Google’s privacy policy here for further information https://www.google.com/privacy.htm

Other cookies may be stored on your computers hard drive by external vendors when this website uses referral programs, sponsored links or adverts. Such cookies are used for conversion and referral tracking and typically expire after 30 days, though some may take longer. No personal information is stored, saved or collected.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.earticleblog.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.earticleblog.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.earticleblog.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or websites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

### Contact & Communication

Users contacting this website and/or its owners do so at their own discretion and provide any such personal details requested at their own risk. Your personal information is kept private and stored securely until a time it is no longer required or has no use, as detailed in the Data Protection Act 1998. Every effort has been made to ensure a safe and secure form to email submission process but advise users using such form to email processes that they do so at their own risk.

This website and its owners use any information submitted to provide you with further information about the products/services they offer or to assist you in answering any questions or queries you may have submitted. This includes using your details to subscribe you to any email newsletter program the website operates but only if this was made clear to you and your express permission was granted when submitting any form to email process. Or whereby you the consumer have previously purchased from or enquired about purchasing from the company a product or service that the email newsletter relates to. This is by no means an entire list of your user rights in regard to receiving email marketing material. Your details are not passed on to any third parties.

### Email Newsletter

This website operates an email newsletter program, used to inform subscribers about products and services supplied by this website. Users can subscribe through an online automated process should they wish to do so but do so at their own discretion. Some subscriptions may be manually processed through a prior written agreement with the user.

### Adverts and Sponsored Links

This website may contain sponsored links and adverts. These will typically be served through our advertising partners, to whom may have detailed privacy policies relating directly to the adverts they serve.

Clicking on any such adverts will send you to the advertisers website through a referral program which may use cookies and will track the number of referrals sent from this website. This may include the use of cookies which may in turn be saved on your computers hard drive. Users should therefore note they click on sponsored external links at their own risk and this website and its owners cannot be held liable for any damages or implications caused by visiting any external links mentioned.

### Social Media Platforms

Communication, engagement, and actions taken through external social media platforms that this website and its owners participate on are custom to the terms and conditions as well as the privacy policies held with each social media platform respectively.

Users are advised to use social media platforms wisely and communicate/engage upon them with due care and caution in regard to their own privacy and personal details. This website nor its owners will ever ask for personal or sensitive information through social media platforms and encourage users wishing to discuss sensitive details to contact them through primary communication channels such as by telephone or email.

This website may use social sharing buttons which help share web content directly from web pages to the social media platform in question. Users are advised before using such social sharing buttons that they do so at their own discretion and note that the social media platform may track and save your request to share a web page respectively through your social media platform account.

**About us –**

**we are only sharing this tweaks for information and educational purpose only. We are not promoting any hacks & fraudulent activity. **

**Disclaimer:-**

  * This is a promotional SITE only, All files placed here are for introducing purpose only.
  * Please, buy original games/ contents from author or developer site!
  * We try to provide authentic information only. In case if you found information than let us know for correction . We are not liable legally for any information provided Here.  

  * All The Tricks,moding software and Tips are Not my site creation it is taking by some Useful internet resources.so I am not responsible any thing.
  * If you do not agree to all the terms, please disconnect from this site now itself.
  * By remaining at this site, you affirm your understanding and compliance of the above disclaimer and absolve this site of any responsibility henceforth-All files found on this site have been collected from various sources across the web and are believed to be in the “public domain”.
  * All the logos and stuff are the property of their respective owners.
  * We Provides 3rd Party Authors to Give their view on Offers By writing Here. This Views and comments are Purely author own views .
  * **Disclaimer for post:** _This articles was prepared by the author in his personal capacity. The opinions expressed in the articles are the author’s own and do not necessarily reflect the view EarticleBlog . **Earticleblog or the author does not hold any copyright/trademark of the logo and brand name used in the stories.**_

  * Earticle does Not take any Guarantee of their views and authenticity from where they make such view.-If you are the rightful owner of any contents posted here, and object to them being displayed or If you are one of representatives of copy rights department and you don’t like our conditions of store, Please Contact Us with Proper legal data’s.We will remove it in 24 hour!

DMCA Policy Listed Here check Out : [DMCA](https://www.earticleblog.com/dmca)
